var treeQuestions = [
    
{//question 1:
question: "Acer is a genus of trees commonly known by what name?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Oak", "b) River Birch", "c) Maple", "d) Black Walnut"],
flags: [false, false, true, false],
answer: "c) Maple"
},
    
{//question 2:
question: "Which small Colorado city, founded as a mining camp during the Colorado Silver Boom, was later named after the abundance of certain trees in the area?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Elmsly", "b) Ashland", "c) Furn", "d) Aspen"],
flags: [false, false, false, true],
answer: "d) Aspen"
},
    
{//question 3:
question: "What are linden trees commonly called in the UK?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) London tree", "b) Lime Tree", "c) Poplar tree", "d) Tree of Avon"],
flags: [false, true, false, false],
answer: "b) Lime Tree"
},
    
{//question 4:
question: "Pseudotsuga menziesii, an evergreen conifer species native to western North America, has a name which honours a Scottish botanist - what's the name of this tree??",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Douglas fir", "b) Pale Tree", "c) Scotch Pine", "d) Rangoon"],
flags: [true, false, false, false],
answer: "a) Douglas fir"
},
        
{//question 5:
question: "What type of 20 metre tall Christmas tree is normally donated by Norway for Trafalgar Square?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Norwegian", "b) Spruce", "c) Hemlock", "d) Aspen"],
flags: [false, true, false, false],
answer: "b) Spruce"
},
        
{//question 6:
question: "Which popular garden tree, with yellow pea-flowers, are sometimes called golden chain or golden rain?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Elmsly", "b) Peabody", "c) Laburnum", "d) Yellow Giardin"],
flags: [false, false, true, false],
answer: "c) Laburnum"
},
    
{//question 7:
question: "The nuts of which trees in the British Isles are called conkers?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Horse-chestnut", "b) Water Tree", "c) Ironwood", "d) Grey Birch"],
flags: [true, false, false, false],    
answer: "a) Horse-Chestnut"
},
        
{//question 8:
question: "Which trees are a traditional feature of churchyards?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Yew", "b) Sherman Tree", "c) Dogwood", "d) Rhododendron"],
flags: [true, false, false, false],
answer: "a) Yew"
},
        
{//question 9:
question: "Can you name the only country named after a tree?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Chile", "b) Brazil", "c) Angola", "d) Cyprus"],
flags: [false, true, false, false],
answer: "b) Brazil"
},
        
{//question 10:
question: "What is dendrochronology?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Tree Aging", "b) Wound Sealing", "c) Staged Planting", "d) Trimming"],
flags: [true, false, false, false],
answer: "a) Tree Aging"
},
            
{//question 11:
question: "Which genus of trees includes the plums, cherries, peaches, and apricots?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Tomcot", "b) Falstaff", "c) Prunus", "d) Mulberry"],
flags: [false, false, true, false],
answer: "c) Prunus"
},
            
{//question 12:
question: "What is the alternative name of the rowan tree??",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Mountain-ash", "b) River Birch", "c) Poplar", "d) Aspen"],
flags: [true, false, false, false],
answer: "a) Mountain-ash"
},
    
{//question 13:
question: "The bark of which tree is also known as “nature’s aspirin?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Hemlock", "b) River Birch", "c) Willow", "d) Plum tree"],
flags: [false, false, true, false],
answer: "c) Willow"
},
                
{//question 14:
question: "Possibly the most famous tree in the UK, 'The Major Oak’ is found in which forest?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Sherwood Forest", "b) Stratford Apon Avon", "c) Piccadilly Circle", "d) Greenwich Park"],
flags: [true, false, false, false],
answer: "a) Sherwood Forest"
},
                
{//question 15:
question: "What tree features in the middle of the flag of Lebanon??",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Cedar", "b) Blackthorn", "c) Buckthorn", "d) Elmsly"],
flags: [false, false, false, true],
answer: "a) Cedar"
}
];